const data = [
  {
    question: "What is Lorem Ipsum?",
    answer: "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s."
  },
  {
    question: "Why do we use it?",
    answer: "It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content of a page when looking at its layout."
  },
  {
    question: "Where does it come from?",
    answer: "Contrary to popular belief, Lorem Ipsum is not simply random text. It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC."
  },
  {
    question: "Where can I get some?",
    answer: "There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available, but the majority have suffered alteration in some form."
  },
  {
    question: "Is Lorem Ipsum safe to use?",
    answer: "Yes, Lorem Ipsum is safe to use as placeholder text in design and publishing."
  },
  {
    question: "Who created Lorem Ipsum?",
    answer: "Lorem Ipsum comes from sections of 'de Finibus Bonorum et Malorum' by Cicero, written in 45 BC."
  },
  {
    question: "Can Lorem Ipsum be translated?",
    answer: "Lorem Ipsum is pseudo-Latin and does not translate to meaningful text, but its origins can be traced to real Latin."
  },
  {
    question: "Is Lorem Ipsum used worldwide?",
    answer: "Yes, Lorem Ipsum is used by designers and publishers all over the world as placeholder text."
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of Lorem Ipsum?",
    answer: "The purpose is to provide a natural looking block of text that doesn't distract from the layout."
  },
  {
    question: "Are there alternatives to Lorem Ipsum?",
    answer: "Yes, there are other placeholder texts like 'Bacon Ipsum', 'Hipster Ipsum', and 'Cupcake Ipsum'."
  }
];

export default data;